<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on void</title>
    <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on void</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nyx-void.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Do</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p align=center&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consuming can make a person more knowledgable. There is value in knowledge. But there can be no positive change until you create.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Distraction is fear. Recognize it in you, feel it, spend a moment with it, thank it and then choose the other path. Do! Create, engage and help.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you consume, put your intention into love and be with yourself, whole and aware. Otherwise put your intention into love, and do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise Above</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/rise_above/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/rise_above/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In life, challenges often seem insurmountable, obstacles loom large, and doubts whisper in the shadows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yet, it is during these moments of adversity that our true strength is revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In tough times, we rise strong like the phoenix, flying past limits, powered by our resilience and steadfast faith.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like a phoenix rising from the ashes, we have the power to transcend limitations and soar to new heights. With resilience as our wings and determination as our compass, we navigate through turbulent skies, guided by the unwavering belief that within us lies the capacity to overcome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeds</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/seeds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“The dream is a little hidden door in the innermost and most secret recesses of the soul, opening into that cosmic night which was psyche long before there was any ego-consciousness, and which will remain psyche no matter how far our ego-consciousness extends.” — Carl G. Jung&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Within lucid dreams, you can soar through the cosmos, turn your demons into flowers and make love to angels. You can interact with a dream-like world and channel your conscious energies into your subconscious dream state.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/social_media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/social_media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p align=center&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you ever think that using social media, or what I like to call &amp;ldquo;stupid media&amp;rdquo;, from a tiny corner of your room makes you a step away from society or being social? Think about it, you&amp;rsquo;re wasting hours of your precious life scrolling through feeds, liking and commenting on posts that are utterly irrelevant to your existence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I mean, no, why should I think about it? Mind your own business, I use these platforms just for fun, I enjoy scrolling through my phone screen&amp;hellip; But let&amp;rsquo;s be real, we both know that&amp;rsquo;s just a lie. We&amp;rsquo;re all addicted to the constant stream of information, and we&amp;rsquo;re too afraid to admit it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twice Dead</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/twice_dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/twice_dead/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p align=center&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;      When I was done dying,&#xA;      my conscious regained&#xA;      So I began the struggle,&#xA;      a nothingness strained&#xA;                - Dan Deacon&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the dimly lit corridors of Westbrook High, a tale of resilience and redemption unfolded, centering around a girl named Gai. Gai’s story was unlike any other, marked by the haunting shadows of tragedy and the relentless pursuit of a second chance. Gai had faced death not once, but twice, in the unforgiving twists of fate that shaped her life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Student&#39;s Tale: Navigating College and Code</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/posts/second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/posts/second-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;and the occasional crush. As a BCA student at Butwal Kalika Campus,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m diving headfirst into the world of computer science. C++ is my weapon of choice, and I&amp;rsquo;m constantly sharpening my skills to tackle the challenges ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Follow along as I juggle assignments, projects, and maybe even a little romance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;#BCAStudent #C&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Embrace the challenges ahead as opportunities for growth. Like sharpening a blade, each obstacle in the world of computer science hones our skills and fortifies our resolve.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing the Linux Lifestyle</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Say hello to efficiency and customization with Linux! As an avid Arch Linux user, I&amp;rsquo;ve found the perfect balance of performance and flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From tweaking system configurations to exploring the depths of the command line, every day is a new adventure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Join me on the journey to open-source greatness!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;#ArchLinux #OpenSource #Efficiency&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Download GNU Arch linux and get ready for clean UI experience.(BTW)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-Download&#34; data-lang=&#34;Download&#34;&gt;Certainly! For more information, please visit the following URL&#xA;&#xA;$&amp;gt;  https://archlinux.org/&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Development</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/posts/fourth_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/posts/fourth_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;simplicity-is-core-to-my-software-development-because-it-leads-to&#34;&gt;Simplicity is core to my software development, because it leads to;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;fewer bugs,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;better performance,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;lower memory footprint,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;better maintainability,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;higher scalability,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;longer software lifetime,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;prompt delivery;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;…all of which lead to a better quality finished product.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Heart&#39;s Melody: Musings on Crushes</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/posts/third-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/posts/third-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The journey of a crush is a captivating one. It&amp;rsquo;s a journey filled with wonder and uncertainty, where every interaction becomes a treasure to cherish.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So next time you find yourself lost in a sea of crimson, embrace the moment with a wink and a smile. After all, blushing is simply your heart&amp;rsquo;s way of saying,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Live a life that&amp;rsquo;s both chill and meaningful - find moments of serenity amidst the chaos, and purpose in every step you take. Embrace the journey, savor the small joys, and inspire others along the way.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome&#34;&gt;Welcome!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am an open-source enthusiast and dedicated programmer with a passion for crafting elegant and efficient code. My primary programming languages are Rust and C, which I use to create software that is both reliable and performant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am deeply committed to the principles of minimalism, particularly in software development. My expertise lies in designing solutions that are straightforward yet powerful, ensuring that they are easy to maintain and deliver exceptional performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
