<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on void</title>
    <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing on void</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Do</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p align=center&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consuming can make a person more knowledgable. There is value in knowledge. But there can be no positive change until you create.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Distraction is fear. Recognize it in you, feel it, spend a moment with it, thank it and then choose the other path. Do! Create, engage and help.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you consume, put your intention into love and be with yourself, whole and aware. Otherwise put your intention into love, and do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise Above</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/rise_above/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/rise_above/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In life, challenges often seem insurmountable, obstacles loom large, and doubts whisper in the shadows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yet, it is during these moments of adversity that our true strength is revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In tough times, we rise strong like the phoenix, flying past limits, powered by our resilience and steadfast faith.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like a phoenix rising from the ashes, we have the power to transcend limitations and soar to new heights. With resilience as our wings and determination as our compass, we navigate through turbulent skies, guided by the unwavering belief that within us lies the capacity to overcome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeds</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/seeds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“The dream is a little hidden door in the innermost and most secret recesses of the soul, opening into that cosmic night which was psyche long before there was any ego-consciousness, and which will remain psyche no matter how far our ego-consciousness extends.” — Carl G. Jung&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Within lucid dreams, you can soar through the cosmos, turn your demons into flowers and make love to angels. You can interact with a dream-like world and channel your conscious energies into your subconscious dream state.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/social_media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/social_media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p align=center&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you ever think that using social media, or what I like to call &amp;ldquo;stupid media&amp;rdquo;, from a tiny corner of your room makes you a step away from society or being social? Think about it, you&amp;rsquo;re wasting hours of your precious life scrolling through feeds, liking and commenting on posts that are utterly irrelevant to your existence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I mean, no, why should I think about it? Mind your own business, I use these platforms just for fun, I enjoy scrolling through my phone screen&amp;hellip; But let&amp;rsquo;s be real, we both know that&amp;rsquo;s just a lie. We&amp;rsquo;re all addicted to the constant stream of information, and we&amp;rsquo;re too afraid to admit it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twice Dead</title>
      <link>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/twice_dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:00:43 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nyx-void.github.io/writing/twice_dead/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p align=center&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;      When I was done dying,&#xA;      my conscious regained&#xA;      So I began the struggle,&#xA;      a nothingness strained&#xA;                - Dan Deacon&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the dimly lit corridors of Westbrook High, a tale of resilience and redemption unfolded, centering around a girl named Gai. Gai’s story was unlike any other, marked by the haunting shadows of tragedy and the relentless pursuit of a second chance. Gai had faced death not once, but twice, in the unforgiving twists of fate that shaped her life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
